["YOU'RE MY FAVORITE SONG"
BY PRINCESS ALIYAH]
Previously on You're
My Favorite Song...
We're buried in debt,
we spent everything we had,
but we made it.
We can finally have
our grand opening!
This next song is also original,
and I wrote it for someone
who isn't here.
♪ Feelings inside my chest ♪
♪ Rising up to my throat ♪
I just need a scratch paper.
- Bro.
- Excuse me.
Excuse me!
Hey, what are you doing to him?
Stop it.
- She's got guts.
- You're pretty bold.
Miss Transferee,
for your information,
Calix is the smartest student
here at Brighton Bay Academy.
No one can beat him
academically, okay?
Know your place.
Sorry.
You got dragged into this.
Here at Brighton Academy,
where you sit really matters.
I am going to be giving
a diagnostic exam.
She's also the one who always
gives a bonus question in exams.
No one ever gets it
because it's so difficult.
Serina?
She's Mom Bebe's
younger sister.
But she left home
after we had a falling out.
I'm sorry.
No matter what offer you make,
no matter how expensive,
no matter how big,
we will not accept it because
maybe you don't understand
how important
- this place is to our family.
- [XAVI CHUCKLES]
Family?
[SCOFFS]
I was once part
of that wretched family,
remember?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
♪ 'Cause baby,
you are my favorite song ♪
♪ I'll put you on repeat
all night ♪
♪ I know I'll never move on ♪
♪ My first,
right where I belong ♪
♪ You are my first
heartbeat song ♪
Sell this resort to me
or else,
we're going to have a problem.
For almost 17 years, Serina,
you never reached out to us.
We've been looking for you.
Looking for me?
Why would you even look for me,
when you already have your
favorite child with you,
the one you always defend,
right?
Because in your eyes,
I was always the black sheep.
That's not true, Serina.
I treated both of you equally.
Come on, my child.
Stop calling me "child,"
you old.
Because of you,
my life was ruined.
Because of you, my child died.
Serina, can you stop
disrespecting Dad like that?
You're the one who
ruined your life.
You were the one who left
that night,
that's why you had
that accident.
Oh, I see.
You know,
you're still the same, Beverly.
The goody goody,
good for nothing
eldest daughter.
But look at you,
and look at me.
Now,
which one of us
actually succeeded?
You have until 5 P.M. today,
not a second more.
If you don't sell me
this resort,
I'll make sure you shut down.
Serina, my child,
- we can talk this through.
- Dad.
- Sir, Sir, Sir, Sir.
- Serina.
- Let go of my father.
- Let him go.
Let's talk about this.
Dad, that's enough.
What she's leaving again.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Stop calling me "child,"
you're old.
Because of you,
my life was ruined.
But look at you, and look at me.
Which one of us
actually succeeded?
Thank you, thank you.
Lady Mara, thank you
for feeding me.
I haven't eaten for two days.
Oh my, just go ahead and eat.
Don't worry, I'll talk to
the Montaverde family
and see if one of our staff here
in the mansion can take you in.
Is the story
about the missing princess
of the family...
Montaverde?
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
You know,
my family has served
the Montaverde family
for generations, and it's true.
Yes, the Montaverde
princess is truly missing.
But you know,
deep inside, I feel it,
I can sense it,
that she's still alive.
And I'm sure
that Celestine inherited
her father's courage
and her mother's intelligence.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
Everybody, settle down.
Settle down.
All right, I've finished
checking your papers.
I'm now going to announce
who got the highest score.
Well, what's new?
It's definitely Calix.
He always gets a perfect score.
Yes, nice one.
- Go, Calix.
- Calix.
Calix.
Yes, it's Calix,
100 out of 100.
[STUDENTS APPLAUDING]
But...
he is not the highest.
- Huh?
- What?
For the first time
in the history
of Brighton Bay Academy,
someone answered
my bonus question.
[INTRIGUING MUSIC PLAYING]
[STUDENTS MURMURING]
Miss Angel Dimaculangan?
What?
One hundred fifty
out of one hundred.
Wait.
Did I hear that correctly,
Ma'am,
150 out of 100?
That's even higher
than a perfect score?
Yes.
One hundred fifty
out of one hundred.
And I think
we now have a new top student
here at Brighton Bay Academy.
[STUDENTS APPLAUDING]
I will now be changing
the seating arrangements
because of the diagnostic exam.
Angel...
You will now be in row two,
seat eight.
[QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING]
And then, Finn,
you will move up to row three.
Yes, Ma'am.
From row two,
I'm going back to row three?
[GUITAR STRUMMING]
Thank you.
[STRUMMING CONTINUES]
Your new house here in Solmera
City is beautiful.
You even have your own studio.
It's much quieter here
than in Manila.
Yeah, dad wants me to finish the
album we're writing for Siklab.
Yeah, as his moneymaking
machine.
Hey, I'm joking, I'm joking.
[CLICKS TONGUE]
I'll continue busking here
in Solmera
while wearing my Captain
Serenade persona.
Maybe I'll do it in front
of Brighton Bay Academy.
Who's that girl again,
the one you became friends with?
The one who gave you
the nickname.
Angel?
I wonder if I'll see her again.
She never came back
to Manila Park.
I will be uploading
the seating arrangements later.
I just have something
very important to attend
to at the faculty.
But please,
remain quiet.
Okay? While I'm gone.
Angel, please hand these test
papers to your classmates.
Yes, Ma'am Dragona.
Thank you.
[SOFT TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[ANGEL GASPS]
Smart, but apparently blind.
Maybe she belongs in row one
with the visually challenged.
[LAUGHS]
[DASH LAUGHS]
- Bro...
- [RAVIEL GROANS]
- I like her.
- What is your problem, really?
Are all of you crazy or what?
So,
you're actually smart.
Your paper.
Let me help you.
There, karma.
[CHUCKLES]
- Deserved.
- Ma'am said
you should distribute
our test papers, right?
Our test papers
are on the floor,
so pick them up.
So,
you're actually smart.
Your paper.
Let me help you.
There, karma.
- Deserved.
- Ma'am said
you should distribute
our test papers, right?
Our test papers
are on the floor,
so pick them up.
Sixteen years ago,
there was born the only princess
of the Montaverde family,
Celestine Montaverde.
[ENRICO PLAYING "I'LL
BE THERE" ON PIANO]
Sir Enrico even wrote a song
for their child of Miss Isabela,
Celestine Montaverde.
Thank you so, so much for
the love you've shown our child.
Oh, Ma'am.
You've also treated us
so well here in the mansion.
So please don't worry,
Ma'am Isabella,
we will love and take care
of Celestine.
We'll treat her like a princess.
[ISABELLA AND MARA LAUGH]
Come here.
Come here, come here.
- [SPEAKS GIBBERISH]
- There you go, come here now.
There, there.
I know, I can feel
that Celestine inherited
Sir Enrico's strength
and courage who,
aside from being a businessman,
is also a military reservist.
And she also got
Ma'am Isabella's beauty
and remarkable intelligence.
[MARA AND ISABELLA LAUGH]
They say Ma'am Isabella speaks
ten languages.
- [MOUTHS]
- Thank you.
But
on Celestine's first birthday...
[LAUGHS]
[VASE CLATTERS]
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYIG]
She was kidnapped
by unknown men.
Years passed,
but she was never found.
They said you didn't eat again.
Your condition
is only getting worse.
[ISABELLA SNIFFLES]
It's been five years...
searching for our child, Enrico.
We still haven't found
Celestine.
[ISABELLA SNIFFLES]
Isabel?
Isabel.
When Ma'am Isabella
passed away...
Isabel.
this mansion lost all its color.
[ENRICO SOBS]
[ENRICO PLAYING "I'LL BE THERE"
ON PIANO]
But Sir Enrico still plays the
song he wrote for Celestine.
He hopes the missing princess
will hear it
and come back to us.
Love.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Come on, let's eat.
Okay, I'll follow.
But a lot has changed.
Four years ago,
Miss Serina arrived
at the mansion.
Sir Enrico fell in love
with her and married her.
But you know,
now that they're married,
her true,
terrible nature has come out.
I really hope Celestine
is still alive.
And I hope
she can return here someday.
I hope
your words come true.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Here, let me help you, Angel.
Are you happy now?
There, hopefully you won't drop
it again next time.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Don't worry,
no one will see us here.
I just want to busk here.
I'm just being careful.
Someone might ask
for a photo with you.
If your dad finds out,
who's also the very strict
manager of our band,
that you're here,
we're in trouble.
I'm just hoping, Jacob.
That Angel might be here
at Manila Park
since this is where
you met before?
What if she comes back, right?
[JACOB CLICKS TONGUE]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Crap, it's Dad.
[GRIPPING MUSIC PLAYING]
Miguel.
Miguel!
Miguel,
what are you doing here
wearing that stupid costume?
[GRIPPING MUSIC INTENSIFIES]
Find out tomorrow
on You're My Favorite Song...
This is our row for today.
Oh, did you hear that?
- You heard that, right?
- You should know,
aside from Calix,
she's someone you shouldn't
mess with.
What do you mean?
I just thought about Serina.
Her anger toward us is intense.
Do you want me to talk to her,
Dad?
I'll tell her about your cancer.
Here's the payment.
I'll add more, just make sure
you do your job well.
Yes.
Leave it to us, Miss Serina.
Their grand opening
will not happen.
All right, leave now.
Are you seriously
saying that to my face?
I'm your wife now
and Celestine is presumed dead.
You're just wasting your time.
If anything happens to him,
all his wealth will go to you.
Are you suggesting
we kill Enrico?
I'm not afraid of you, Calix.
Do it, Calix.
Punch her.
Yeah, she deserves it.
Bro, Bro.
Hey, my bag!
["YOU'RE MY FAVORITE SONG"
BY PRINCESS ALIYAH]
Wait, this bag...
I know this bag.
There.
If it's okay with you,
I can lift you up.
You seem familiar.
Yup, it's me, Angel.
[CHUCKLES]
- [CLAPPING]
- We were amazing.
Come on, smile,
we're in the lead.
♪ 'Cause baby,
you are my favorite song ♪